<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stefanos Vardalos</title>
    <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Stefanos Vardalos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 10:30:00 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stefvardalos.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>MacBook : Dev Setup</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/macbook/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Oct 2018 10:30:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/macbook/</guid>
      <description>MacBook : Dev Setup I have been using mostly linux for many years now but, I just got a new Macbook Pro (2018). I had moderate previous experience with macOS before but I never had one of these machines as my main gear. After my initial &amp;ldquo;wow&amp;rdquo; moments with its screen and some &amp;ldquo;wtf&amp;rdquo; moments with its (lack of) ports, I started migrating my enviroment and searching for whatever I had to install to make this beast my own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CookList : From idea to project to finished app</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/cooklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2018 10:30:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/cooklist/</guid>
      <description>Turning an idea to side project to finished app Every developer should try to have some time to work on a side project, either to improve his development skills, or to feed his creativity hunger. That can be tough having a full time job but, the beauty of the side project is that you can work on it on your own pace. The first step is to find an idea that you would want to work on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Serving your application using Nginx</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/nginx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 10:30:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/nginx/</guid>
      <description>Serving your application using Nginx You have created a web application and now you are searching for the right web server to use to serve it. Your application might consist of multiple static files (HTML , CSS , Javascript etc) and a backend API service or even, multiple webservices . Using Nginx might be the what you are looking for, and there are couple of reasons for that. NGINX can be a powerful web server, using a non-threaded, event-driven architecture that enables him to outperform Apache, but can also do other important things, like load balancing, caching or used as a reverse proxy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Becoming Associate Android Developer, Certified by Google!</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/androidcertified/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2017 10:30:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/androidcertified/</guid>
      <description>Becoming Associate Android Developer, Certified by Google! If you already work with Android Development or you just want to start your journey on mobile development, there is a way to certify your skills and make yourself stand out. Google has introduced the Associate Android Developer Certification back at 2016 and in their words, their aim was to close the gap between developers launching their careers and employers.
By passing this exam and earning the Associate Android Developer Certification, the candidate will be able to demonstrate tested knowledge of Android Development and ability to perform general development tasks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Static sites are BACK!</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/static-site-generators/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 12:15:16 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/static-site-generators/</guid>
      <description>Static sites are BACK! Way back in the day, web pages were just static sites, with only HTML and CSS (and later some JavaScript maybe). Just try to remember what that actually means. There were no server code or database, there was only an .html file hosted somewhere that your browser downloaded and displayed to you. Their development was done in the text files directly or, oh god, through programs like the notorious Dreamweaver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You should have better logging now!</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/js-logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 11:20:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/js-logging/</guid>
      <description>*I have no idea what is going on…* You should have better logging now! There is a part of software development that not all developers take very seriously. That part is proper logging and everyone who has lost countless hours during debugging knows exactly what I mean.
Useful logs can provide the developer ( especially when someone has to debug/maintain someone else’s code ) with tremendous help when trying to understand what the code actually does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS FRAMEWORK TO USE WITH ANGULAR VERSION 2&#43;</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/css-angular/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 18:54:16 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/css-angular/</guid>
      <description>CSS FRAMEWORK TO USE WITH ANGULAR VERSION 2+ While working on a project with Angular 4, I had to choose a CSS framework to built its layout with. Interestingly enough, CSS frameworks haven&amp;rsquo;t yet moved on to component based architecture with the same speed that JS Frameworks have, but there are some quite good choices to work with.
Angular Material It is maintained by Angular Team and of course it&amp;rsquo;s their recommendation for a UI solution, but it is in its relative early steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CookList</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/projects/cooklist/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 10:53:45 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/projects/cooklist/</guid>
      <description>This app is build on Angular, NodeJS and MongoDB.
A theme from HTML5UP is used
All artists and track data are fetched from the Spotify API.
Playlist&amp;rsquo;s cover images are fetched from Unsplash API.
It is hosted on Google Cloud, deployed using Docker and Kubernetes.
Click here to learn more or here to try it out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faction Randomizer for SmashUp</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/projects/smashup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 10:53:45 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/projects/smashup/</guid>
      <description>This is an Android application build on Ionic Framework.
It is an application that helps players of the SmashUp board game to set it up easier / faster.
You can download it from Google PlayStore by clicking here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PickAMovie</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/projects/pickamovie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 10:53:45 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/projects/pickamovie/</guid>
      <description>This is an Android application build on Java.
It is an application that helps user to find a movie to watch, based on the responses they give on some questions.
It uses the TMDb API to query and fetch info about Movies.
You can download it from Google PlayStore by clicking here.
You can check its Privacy Policy here</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PickAMovie Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/custom/pickamovie/privacy_policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 10:53:45 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/custom/pickamovie/privacy_policy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy Stefanos Vardalos built the PickAMovie app as an Ad Supported app. This SERVICE is provided by Stefanos Vardalos at no cost and is intended for use as is.
This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>StefVardalos.github.io</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/projects/stefvardalos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2017 10:53:45 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/projects/stefvardalos/</guid>
      <description>This is static webpage / blog build using the Hugo Framework.
A theme originally developed from HTML5UP is used, ported to Hugo by *jpescador.
It is hosted on GitHub Pages.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>