<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Stefanos Vardalos</title>
    <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Stefanos Vardalos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 12:15:16 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Static sites are BACK!</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/static-site-generators/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 12:15:16 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/static-site-generators/</guid>
      <description>Static sites are BACK! Way back in the day, web pages were just static sites, with only HTML and CSS (and later some JavaScript maybe). Just try to remember what that actually means. There were no server code or database, there was only an .html file hosted somewhere that your browser downloaded and displayed to you. Their development was done in the text files directly or, oh god, through programs like the notorious Dreamweaver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You should have better logging now!</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/js-logging/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 11:20:00 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/js-logging/</guid>
      <description>I have no idea what is going on…
You should have better logging now! There is a part of software development that not all developers take very seriously. That part is proper logging and everyone who has lost countless hours during debugging knows exactly what I mean.
Useful logs can provide the developer ( especially when someone has to debug/maintain someone else’s code ) with tremendous help when trying to understand what the code actually does.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSS FRAMEWORK TO USE WITH ANGULAR VERSION 2&#43;</title>
      <link>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/css-angular/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jun 2017 18:54:16 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stefvardalos.github.io/blog/css-angular/</guid>
      <description>CSS FRAMEWORK TO USE WITH ANGULAR VERSION 2+ While working on a project with Angular 4, I had to choose a CSS framework to built its layout with. Interestingly enough, CSS frameworks haven&amp;rsquo;t yet moved on to component based architecture with the same speed that JS Frameworks have, but there are some quite good choices to work with.
Angular Material It is maintained by Angular Team and of course it&amp;rsquo;s their recommendation for a UI solution, but it is in its relative early steps.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>